[MITHRIL]
Really?
Anne, are you being serious?
[ANNE]
Yes.
Are you sure?
But the crest of House Chamber
is supposed to be a taboo!
Do you have any idea?
[MITHRIL]
Oh!
Well, all right.
Then I'll help you.
Need some pigment powder?
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
I need purple, red, and blue
and green and black, as well.
Leave it to me!
Oh, and everything
that's close, if you don't mind!
Sure!
[ANNE] A crest is the pride
of a noble family.
And in Noah's eyes
the crest of House Chamber
is almost like
Lord Herbert's spirit
in physical form.
That's why he watches over it.
♪
Even if the symbol is forbidden
it still matters to him.
He's been gazing at it
all this time!
♪
Is it done now?
[ANNE]
Yes. It's done.
We did it, Anne!
Hooray! Great work!
I knew you'd pull through!
Oh, and its look amazing.
[HUGH]
It sounds like a party in here.
Let's go. The time's come.
We won't tell
Noah this was a contest.
If his pride gets in the way,
he may keep refusing.
[knocks]
[creaks]
Noah. Are you awake?
Huh!
[NOAH]
Hmm-uh! Silver Sugar Viscount?
Like I said yesterday,
here's a present
for your kindness.
[gasps]
♪
[ANNE]
A fief set.
How did Hugh know about that?
So, what do you think?
For the board, I figured I could
use the one in the lesser hall.
What?
[HUGH] As you know the pieces
were unfortunately lost
when the castle was looted.
However, the Church
of Saint Lewiston Bell
still had some sketches,
so I was able to study those.
Uh-Huh!
Hmm!
I also learned your lord
had mastered the game.
Huh! My lord a fief master,
you must be mistaken
he was terrible at it.
And that's why no one else
would play it with him.
Oh, well, naturally
they wouldn't.
Why would someone challenge him?
The greatest master in the land?
The greatest master?
[gasps]
[HUGH]
But you didn't know that,
so you had no problem
asking him to play.
I imagine that made
Lord Herbert very happy.
That you wanted a game.
Not to compete,
but purely for fun.
♪
So, Lord Herbert.
Do with the pieces as you wish.
They're yours now,
like the old ones.
Huh! I see!
He might be even more likely to
eat something small like that.
♪
But should I?
[sobs]
Noah,
we've brought along another
present for you, as well.
Hm! This belongs to you, too!
Because I made it for you.
[gasps]
♪
Could it be? Yes!
The crest
of Lord Herbert's house!
This is beautiful!
Like it?
Hmm!
I'm so glad.
[gasps]
[ANNE] I hope he can feel,
even if just a little,
that the heart of his master
lies in that crest.
♪
[sighs]
[NOAH]
I just ate it.
Did I?
Yes, it's gone!
But I... I was! [sniffles]
[HUGH]
Noah.
Here.
♪
I don't understand, sir.
Eat as many as you want.
I can assure you
he won't be angry.
But then I think
you know that, don't you?
[gasps]
[sniffles]
If it dwells in your heart,
that crest will never fade.
[NOAH]
Lord Herbert.
[sniffles] Whatever they say.
Lord Herbert
truly did live here.
He played fief with me,
ate sugar confections.
He was here!
Smiling and having fun!
And laughing with me.
[sniffles]
I'll never forget...
the fun we had!
When he was here.
[sniffles]
[HUGH]
That crest has been banned.
That confection
that you made him,
it will be seen as
a defiance of the crown.
Didn't you hesitate?
Even for a moment?
You're a silver sugar master!
Just a little but still
I made something that someone
else desperately needed.
If that's so bad, then why even
be a silver sugar master?
[gasps]
Hmm!
Of course.
That's why you're a success.
Ah!
[HUGH]
After all.
That crest represents
the spirit of this house.
In a way, it serves as proof
that the person
who bore it actually existed.
And Noah's fully aware
of that fact
which is why he sees
his master's heart inside it.
But if you understood that
then why didn't you make
the crest too?
[HUGH]
I did make it one time.
[gasps]
But I destroyed it.
I'm the Silver Sugar Viscount
and a servant of the crown.
That crest is taboo according
to House Millsland
and the royal family.
So, I dare not depict it.
Tell me something, Hugh.
Why did you become
the Silver Sugar Viscount
if you can only make the pieces
you're told to make?
Hmm! You know something?
Kat asked me that too.
"That power," he said,
"Is it honestly worth giving up
your freedom?"
You should've seen
how angry he was that day.
And the truth is,
I did want the power badly
enough to sacrifice freedom.
Because without power,
some things
just aren't possible.
Confections can be
imbued with prayers,
but I needed
something more direct.
Well, that's enough talking.
We've got some important
business.
Go ahead and call him in.
[ANNE] So, if Hugh had made
the crest instead, then...
[NADIR]
Hey, Anne!
[laughs] You're amazing!
We found out that you won!
Hmm!
I just overheard Elliott talking
with the Silver Sugar Viscount
about it right now!
Which means Mr. Kat is going to
help us finish our work, right?
[ELLIOTT]
Precisely!
[ANNE]
Mister Collins.
I'll go tell everyone the news!
[ELLIOTT]
The Viscount told me the gist
of how the competition went.
[ANNE]
I don't really think I won.
[chuckles] Well, winner or not,
you solved our problem.
Shouldn't that be enough?
Anne. You did it.
Mister Collins.
Anyway! I'll get back to work!
You should go rest for a bit,
Anne.
I'm guessing you probably
stayed up all night worrying.
If that causes you
to make mistakes,
we'll all be in trouble.
Hmm! I'll keep that in mind.
Challe!
♪
[CHALLE]
Noah's calmer now.
It would appear
your work has helped him a lot.
Wonderful!
Hmm! You did well.
[gasps]
Hmm!
♪
[creaks]
Uh! What do you want?
I wasn't just sitting here
staring at them!
♪
[creaks]
[ANNE] Oh. Where's the one
Hugh gave you?
I haven't seen it, so,
I suppose the Viscount
may have wanted it back?
Ha!
Um, but would you mind asking
him if I could keep it, though?
I promise, I would treasure it
for the rest of my life.
Really. Do you think
he would give it to me?
Sure. I can ask him.
It was a gift for you,
after all.
- I think he'll say yes.
- Good!
[ANNE] That's odd. I don't see
why he would take it with him.
[NOAH] Um. So, your name
isn't thief, it's, uh...
I'm Anne.
Right. Tell me, Anne.
Why did you give those
two fairies their wings back?
Is it because they weren't
useful to you?
Noah.
Even though Lord Herbert
was so kind, he used to lie.
He said that he was bad at fief
when he was a champion.
What else was a lie?
Why did he really leave me
behind?
Was it because I was
useless to him, after all?
♪
The reason I gave them back
their wings
is because I see them
the way I see myself.
We're friends,
and we're all equal.
So, it's not right
to order them around.
What?
In Lord Herbert's case
maybe, you were that important
to him as well
and that's why he set you free.
He cared about you very much.
Uh-huh!
Do you really think that was it?
Mmm-hmm! And he adored you.
Now then, why not rest
a little while,
if you do then you will
have even more energy!
[NOAH]
All right.
♪
Anne, stay here and hold my hand
until I fall asleep, would you?
I will.
[sighs]
♪
[HERBERT] I'm grateful.
Silver Sugar Master.
Because of you,
I too can leave this castle
with a peaceful heart.
At long last.
[ANNE]
Lord Herbert.
For this year's Pull Soul Day,
I'll make a sugar confection
in your honor.
And then,
I know you'll make it to heaven.
[ORLAND] Now we can finally do
the assembly work we put off.
Right! Anne saved the day!
You know. Anne made him a crest
and it was even better
than the fief set
that the Viscount made!
I wish I could have seen
his work for myself.
Would be an honor.
So, she did win.
Where's Gladus?
[creaks]
Are you here, Gladus? It's me.
[footsteps]
What are you doing?
Huh!
♪
Isn't that?
Oh, it's just you.
[BRIDGET]
Wait, don't eat that!
It was crafted for that child
fairy who was starving!
It's to bring him happiness!
He's the only one
who's permitted to have it!
You have no business
laying your hands on it!
[gasps]
Be quiet.
[sighs] No!
[groans]
It's giving me so much power!
I'd expect nothing less
from the Viscount. How lovely.
[BRIDGET]
Why?
[LAFALLE]
I was injured.
It took a while to find
something strong enough
to restore me.
So, imagine
my luck finding these.
[BRIDGET]
You used me, didn't you?
[LAFALLE] Indeed, and it
gives me no joy to admit this,
but I didn't feel
even a speck of guilt.
[sighs]
- Oh, what now?
- I think you know!
♪
Ah!
[chuckles]
But why?
[LAFALLE]
Well, that was cruel.
Whoever owns that wing must be
in terrible agony right now.
[BRIDGET]
[gasps] Stay back!
[exhales]
Don't interrupt my meal.
[footsteps]
[LAFALLE]
Found you at last. Brooding?
Tell me honestly!
Why do you desire
to get close to me?
What lovely eyes.
Be serious.
Oh, I am serious.
It's something
that I've envisioned endlessly.
I knew that
the obsidian fairy's eyes
would be incomparably beautiful.
Challe fenn Challe.
As soon as I heard your name,
there could be no doubt.
I was certain that I'd found
someone I had been seeking
for quite a long time.
I never knew your face or name.
The only thing I knew was
that you had been born.
Through unfortunate coincidence,
we two were torn
from each other.
I feared that we may never meet.
Then I gave up hope,
and a century passed.
But now, we're together!
Who are you?
Tell me what your true name is.
I'm so happy you asked.
Lafalle fenn Lafalle.
[gasps]
Lafalle fenn Lafalle?
What's wrong?
It ought to sound familiar
to you, Shall.
Since the moment
that you were born
it has been ringing out
from deep inside your very soul.
The stone that bore me was set
into the hilt of a sword
forgotten to time.
[LAFALLE]
That's right.
A sword enshrined within a
darkened chapel,
as though to hide it.
As you know there was an opal
and a diamond embedded
into the hilt as well.
I am the fairy who came
from that opal
before the obsidian spawned you.
Those three precious stones
were chosen specifically,
with the hope that something
would be born out of them.
By whom?
Who was the one responsible?
Why the sword's master.
You tell me who it was,
immediately!
There's no need to rush.
For at the appropriate moment,
I'll happily explain everything.
What you've asked me
and what you've yet to wonder.
Challe, you must come with me.
You and I are meant to be
together.
Our destiny is predetermined.
The fact we've reunited after
a hundred years should be proof.
[CHALLE]
What did you say?
Free yourself
from humanity's control!
Come away with me!
♪
My fate will
not be decided by you!
I had a feeling you'd say that.
Perhaps if I obtained that girl,
you might be more cooperative.
[CHALLE]
I won't let you have her!
[LAFALLE]
Let me? You can't stop me!
Huh!
So, that was you.
[LAFALLE] I'll admit, the cut
you gave me had quite an effect
but now, thanks
to the Silver Sugar Viscount's
confections,
I'm feeling better than ever.
You're bold to reveal your true
identity to me.
Just don't run away this time.
Well, this is a problem.
You see, my original intention
was to slice you into ribbons
on the spot,
but things have changed now.
Since I don't desire
to hurt you.
I am at a staggering
disadvantage.
So, to even the odds a bit.
♪
I will be taking the girl.
Urgh!
[LAFALLE] That way, you'll
belong to me as well, yes?
She's going to be mine.
[laughs]
Resist all you like
my fate is bound to yours.
Huh!
Anne!
[door opens]
♪
Hmm! Challe? What's wrong?
[gasps]
I won't let you go.
[ANNE]
What happened?
No one will take you.
I gave you my word.
I will protect you.
♪